(Penny:)That's a dollar.
(Bernadette:)Then guess who wildly overtipped
a cocktail waitress.
(Amy:)Hey, Penny... hey, let's go.
(Amy:)We found a place that has
Australian male strippers.
(Bernadette:)We want to see
(Bernadette:)if they twirl their junk
in the other direction.
(Penny:)That sounds so great.
(Penny:)But I have
a little more studying to do.
(sighs) Can you
believe this nerd?
(Bernadette:)Come on, do you want to
sit here being a loser,
(Bernadette:)or do you want to watch me climb
(Bernadette:)into an Australian man's
G-string
(Bernadette:)like a baby kangaroo?
(Penny:)All right, guys, look,
I would love to go out,
(Penny:)but I've got
to get this done, okay?
(Penny:)So have fun at the club.
And if you get
(Penny:)in trouble, find a policeman.
(Penny:)And if he's taking off
his pants,
(Penny:)he is not a real policeman.